A Guide to Production Books for Arena Stage, 1950-2000
George Mason University Libraries
- Arena Stage Production Books and Information
  - The Skin of our Teeth: misc. production materials (Box Box 94)
  - The Skin of our Teeth: blocking script (Box Box 94)
  - A Small World: production book (Box Box 95)
  - A Small World: production script (Box Box 95)
  - A Small World:schs., blocking notes (Box Box 95)
  - A Small World: performance report, script revision (Box Box 95)
  - State of the Union: misc. materials (Box Box 96)
  - State of the Union: misc. materials (Box Box 96)
  - State of the Union: script and production book (Box Box 96)
  - Swan: rehearsal and final script (Box Box 97)
  - Swan: rehearsal and script (Box Box 97)
  - Sunday in the Park with George: calling script, 1 of 2 (Box Box 98)
  - Sunday in the Park with George: calling script, 2 of 2 (Box Box 98)
  - Sunday in the Park with George: blocking script, 1 of 3 (Box Box 98)
  - Sunday in the Park with George: blocking script, 2 of 3 (Box Box 98)
  - Sunday in the Park with George: blocking script, 3 of 3 (Box Box 98)
  - Summer and Smoke: schs., reports, tech notes (Box Box 99)
  - Summer and Smoke: blocking script (Box Box 99)
  - Summer and Smoke: calling script (Box Box 99)
  - Thunder Knocking on the Door: programs, cast list and contact sheet (Box Box 100)
  - Thunder Knocking on the Door: blocking script (Box Box 100)
  - Thunder Knocking on the Door: prop list (Box Box 100)
  - Thunder Knocking on the Door: costumes (Box Box 100)
  - Thunder Knocking on the Door: reh. notes (Box Box 100)
  - Thunder Knocking on the Door: schedules (Box Box 100)
  - Thunder Knocking on the Door: show reports (Box Box 100)
  - Thunder Knocking on the Door: sound/band info (Box Box 100)
  - Thunder Knocking on the Door: spots (Box Box 100)
  - Thunder Knocking on the Door: script revisions (Box Box 100)
  - Thunder Knocking on the Door: reviews (Box Box 100)
  - Thunder Knocking on the Door: memos (Box Box 100)
  - Time of your Life: misc. production materials (Box Box 101)
  - Time of you Life: blocking script (Box Box 101)
  - Time of your Life: misc. stage / pre-set info (Box Box 101)
  - The Time of your Life: pre-set and dressing room info (Box Box 101)
  - Touch of the Poet: production book (Box Box 102)
  - Touch of the Poet: show reports and misc. backstage info (Box Box 102)
  - Touch of the Poet:background packet, costume info, and misc. production materials (Box Box 102)
  - Touch of the Poet: tech notes (Box Box 102)
  - Trinidad Sisters: production book (Box Box 103)
  - Trinidad Sisters: blocking script (Box Box 103)
  - Trinidad Sisters: rehearsal reports, and misc.. info (Box Box 103)
  - Twelfth Night: blocking script (Box Box 104)
  - Twelfth Night:blocking script (Box Box 104)
  - Twelfth Night: tech script (Box Box 104)
  - Twelfth Night: tech script (Box Box 104)
  - Twelfth Night: misc. production material (Box Box 104)
  - Twelfth Night: reh. schs. (Box Box 104)
  - Uncle Vanya: blocking script/calling script (Box Box 105)
  - Uncle Vanya: misc. production materials (Box Box 105)
  - Uncle Vanya: scripts/sch. (Box Box 105)
  - The Visit: blocking script (Box Box 106)
  - The Visit: blocking script (Box Box 106)
  - The Visit: blocking script (Box Box 106)
  - The Visit: stage set up, background info (Box Box 106)
  - The Visit: stage set up, script, production info (Box Box 106)
  - The Visit: costumes and stage info (Box Box 106)
  - Vivisection from the Blown Mind: stage pre-set info (Box Box 107)
  - Vivisection of the Blown Mind: production calender, blocking script (Box Box 107)
  - Vivisections of the Blown Mind: blocking script (Box Box 107)
  - Vivisections from the Blown Mind: misc. production materials (Box Box 107)
  - Voir Dire: cast info, tech info, sch., reports, call board info (Box Box 108)
  - Voir Dire: blocking script 1 of 2 (Box Box 103)
  - Voir Dire: blocking script, 2 of 2 (Box Box 108)
  - Waiting Room: schedules, show reports, misc. paperwork (Box Box 109)
  - The Waiting Room: prompt book (Box Box 109)
  - Way of the World: production book, 1 of 3 (Box Box 110)
  - Way of the World: production book, 2 of 3 (Box Box 110)
  - Way of the World: production book, 3 of 3 (Box Box 110)
  - What the Butler Saw: production book (Box Box 111)
  - The Women: run sheet (Box Box 112)
  - The Women: cue master sheet (Box Box 112)
  - The Women: performance calander (Box Box 112)
  - The Women: contact sheet (Box Box 112)
  - The Women: props (Box Box 112)
  - The Women: program / cast photo (Box Box 112)
  - The Women: script, acting edition w/ blocking notes (Box Box 113)
  - The Women: workers comp / accident reports (Box Box 113)
  - The Women: rehearsal notes (Box Box 113)
  - The Women: rehearsal schedule (Box Box 113)
  - The Women: dressing sheets (Box Box 113)
  - The Women: Costumes (Box Box 113)
  - Wonderful Life: costumes and props info (Box Box 114)
  - Wonderful Life: calling script, 1 of 2 (Box Box 114)
  - Wonderful Life: calling script, 2 of 2 (Box Box 114)
  - Wonderful Life: reports and schedules (Box Box 114)
  - Wonderful Life: blocking script (Box Box 114)
  - Wonderful Life: blocking script (Box Box 114)
  - Wonderful Life: misc. info and call board stuff (Box Box 114)
  - Wonderful Life: crew packet (Box Box 114)
  - Wonderful Life: stage floor plans (Box Box 114)
  - Wonderful Life: master score, 1 of 2 (Box Box 115)
  - Wonderful Life: master score, 2 of 2 (Box Box 115)
  - Yerma: production book (Box Box 116)
  - Yerma: production book (Box Box 116)
  - Yerma: production book (Box Box 116)
  - You Can't take it With You: prop, costume. sound info (Box Box 117)
  - You can't take it with you: production book (Box Box 117)
  - You cant take it with you: script (Box Box 117)
  - You cant take it with you: blocking script (Box Box 117)
  - You cant take it with you: misc materials (Box Box 117)
  - You cant take it with you: blocking script (Box Box 118)
  - You cant take it with you: production book (Box Box 118)
  - you cant take it with you: performance reports (Box Box 118)
  - You've Gotta have Heart: misc. production materials (Box Box 119)
  - You've Gotta have Heart: misc. materials (Box Box 119)
  - Avner the Eccentric: production agreements (Box Box 120)
  - 'Night, Mother: production agreements (Box Box 120)
  - Women and Water: production agreement (Box Box 120)
  - The Regard of Flight: production agreements (Box Box 120)
  - Restoration: production agreements (Box Box 120)
  - The Wild Duck: production agreement (Box Box 120)
  - The Philadelphia Story: production agreements (Box Box 120)
  - Old Times: production agreements (Box Box 120)
  - The Taming of the Shrew: production agreements (Box Box 120)
  - Stray Dogs: production agreements (Box Box 120)
  - Monteith and Rand: production agreements (Box Box 120)
  - Woza Albert: production agreements (Box Box 120)
  - The Tempest: production agreements (Box Box 120)
  - Gospel at Colonus: production agreements (Box Box 120)
  - Passion Play:production agreement (Box Box 120)
  - Man and Superman: production agreements (Box Box 120)
  - Real Estate: production agreements (Box Box 120)
  - Tartuffe: production agreements (Box Box 120)
  - Isn't it Romantic: production agreements (Box Box 120)
  - Execution of Justice: production agreements (Box Box 120)
  - The Dresser: production agreements (Box Box 120)
  - 1983-1984 benefit: general info (Box Box 120)
  - Monteith and Rand: production agreements (Box Box 120)
  - The Importance of Being Earnest: production agreements (Box Box 120)
  - As You Like it: production agreements (Box Box 120)
  - Beyond Therapy: production agreements (Box Box 120)
  - Three Sisters: production agreements (Box Box 120)
  - The Accidental Death of and Anarchist (Box Box 120)
  - Quartermaine's terms: production agreements (Box Box 120)
  - Cloud 9: production agreements (Box Box 121)
  - Happy End: production agreements (Box Box 121)
  - Foolsfire: production agreements (Box Box 121)
  - The Flying Karamazov Brothers: production agreements (Box Box 121)
  - Still Life: production agreements (Box Box 121)
  - Monteith and Rand: production agreements (Box Box 121)
  - On The Razzle: production agreements (Box Box 121)
  - Cymbeline: production agreements (Box Box 121)
  - Home: production agreements (Box Box 121)
  - Imaginary Invalid: production agreements (Box Box 121)
  - Screenplay: production agreements (Box Box 121)
  - Geniuses: production agreements (Box Box 121)
  - Buried Child: production agreements (Box Box 121)
  - Candide: production agreements (Box Box 121)
  - 50's press photo: model of new building and Zelda (Box Box 121)
  - Arena Stage trip to Russia: 1973 (Box Box 121)
  - Fires in the Mirror: flyer distribution (Box Box 121)
  - 1993-94 season opening night invitations list (Box Box 121)
  - I am a Man: press night list (Box Box 121)
  - misc. meeting minutes (1995-1996) (Box Box 121)
  - 1995-1996: silent auction items (Box Box 121)
  - 1994 long range planning document (Box Box 121)
  - 1993-1994 guide listing budget (Box Box 121)
  - 1995-1996 guide listing budget (Box Box 121)
  - 1992-1993 budget files (Box Box 121)
  - 1994-1995 guide listing budget (Box Box 121)
  - playquest: background (Box Box 121)
  - Rubenstein graphic endowment (Box Box 121)
  - Rubenstein graphics: Jasper Johns (Box Box 121)
  - budget/JE/ general ledger (Box Box 122)
  - Rubenstein Graphic Endowment - Animal Crackers (Box Box 122)
  - Rubenstein Graphic Endowment cover art: Buried Child (Box Box 122)
  - Rubenstein Graphic Endowment cover art: Happy End (Box Box 122)
  - Rubenstein Graphics Endowment cover art: 'Night Mother (Box Box 122)
  - Communication meeting minutes, 1990-1991 (Box Box 122)
  - communication meeting minutes, 1991-1992 (Box Box 122)
  - Communications /development bi-weekly meeting minutes,1991-1992 (Box Box 122)
  - marketing meetings, 1990-1991 (Box Box 122)
  - Marketing meeting minutes, 1991-1992 (Box Box 122)
  - Communications Committee, 1990-1991 (Box Box 122)
  - Communications Committee (Box Box 122)
  - growth through innovation: the 1995-1996 communications plan (Box Box 122)
  - Long Range Plan: 1992-1997 (draft) (Box Box 122)
  - Communications Committee: Feb. 1993 (Box Box 122)
  - Communications Committee, 5/93 (Box Box 122)
  - Communications Committee, 11/5/92 (Box Box 122)
  - Communications Committee: 10/01 (Box Box 122)
  - Communications Committee: 9/14/93 (Box Box 122)
  - November 4 Communications Committee (Box Box 122)
  - Communications Committee meeting: Nov. 1993 (Box Box 123)
  - Communications Committee organization (Box Box 123)
  - Communications Committee meeting: March, 1994 (Box Box 123)
  - 1996-1997 income projection and goals (Box Box 123)
  - 1995-1996 income goals per-show (Box Box 123)
  - Communications Committee meeting: January, 1996 (Box Box 123)
  - Communications Committee meetings 1995-1996 (Box Box 123)
  - Communications Committee meeting: Oct. 1995 (Box Box 123)
  - meeting plan presentation: 1995-1996 (Box Box 123)
  - Communications Committee meeting: May 1995 (Box Box 123)
  - marketing minutes 1995-1996 (Box Box 123)
  - Communications Committee meeting: Dec. 1994 (Box Box 123)
  - Communications and Marketing department meetings, 1995 (Box Box 123)
  - interdepartmental minutes, 1955-1996 (Box Box 123)
  - Staff meeting minutes: 1995-1996 (Box Box 123)
  - Communications staff minutes, 1995-1996 (Box Box 123)
  - Communications staff minutes: 1995-1996 (Box Box 123)
  - Marketing Meetings: 1994-1995 (Box Box 123)
  - Marketing meeting and communications dept. meetings minutes (Box Box 123)
  - Marketing goals: 1994-1995 (Box Box 123)
  - Communications Committee meeting: Nov. 94 (Box Box 123)
  - Communications Committee meeting: Jan. 1995 (Box Box 123)
  - Communications Committee: April, 28 (Box Box 123)
  - Communications board meeting: May 1997 (Box Box 124)
  - Communications Committee: 1996-1997 (Box Box 124)
  - Communications Committee meetings: 1997 (Box Box 124)
  - Protix, L.P. June 29, 1995 (Box Box 124)
  - MKTG MTG minutes 1996-1997 (Box Box 124)
  - Communications staff meeting minutes: 1996-1997 (Box Box 124)